JENNY CITHERLET

P: 604 935 6304

E: jennycith@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a resourceful Email specialist and Account Producer with extensive experience in project management. I specialize in HTML/CSS transactional emails and marketing campaigns.

I utilize strong organizational, planning and communication skills towards improving operational efficiency. I work with Agile/Scrum methodologies, and I have a passion for people and technology. With a comprehensive background in digital media and web technologies, I am a problem-solver with excellent analytical and negotiation skills. I am committed to providing the best customer experience as well as continuous improvement.

SKILLS

- 8+ yrs. of experience in email production (HTML, CSS)
- Strong working knowledge of CMS, HTML, CSS, email client specificities, A/B testing
- Dynamic and reliable team-player with proven organizational and communication skills
- Customer service attitude and trustworthy, positive approach. Experience working remotely
- Experience with email best practices CAN-SPAM, GDPR compliance, and EU Spam Laws

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EMAIL / WEB SPECIALIST — CRM Freelance

APRIL 2018 TO PRESENT

- Building collateral (HTML transactional email and marketing campaigns) for clients
- Advocate best practices in email design, content strategy, and digital marketing using CSS to meet design specifications of customers for the specific application
- Built and updated Wordpress pages using Sketch or Figma files
- Conduct email client testing and A/B testing

GUESTFOLIO – CENDYN, WHISTLER, BC ACCOUNT PRODUCER

MAY 2014 - MARCH 2018 MARCH 2017- MARCH 2020 (CONTRACTOR)

- Responsible for on-boarding and building new accounts. Uses creative and digital skills to build collateral (HTML/CSS automated email marketing solution, newsletter, Mobile Concierge app & survey) for our hotel clients worldwide
- Contact clients on a regular basis including in-depth weekly or monthly calls to review campaign performance, suggesting additional email marketing strategies and campaign optimizations to continuously improve results

GROUND OFFICE MANAGER & ADMINISTRATOR

- Managed and trained team of 15 Sales Associates
- Monitored and tracked accounts payable/receivable
- Acted as the main contact for booking agents and provided booking agents with Product Knowledge Sessions
- Built and maintained strong business partnerships to deliver a high level of service
- Created and implemented tools & processes for tracking reservations and seat bookings
- Coordinated administration & communication on a daily basis

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Familiar with CAN-SPAM, GDPR and CASL regulations
- Experience working with Agile methodologies
- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google Docs, Asana, Slack, Teams
- Experience using ERPs (Oracle, SAP)
- Fluent in French/English
- Familiar with SQL

EDUCATION

0	Web Development Bootcamp	Lighthouse Labs, Vancouver, BC	2020
0	Digital Marketing & Social Media	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2019
0	Web Technologies	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2013
0	Business Diploma	Ecole Supérieure de Commerce, Switzerland	2002

LAUGUAGES

Fluent in French, English and professional working proficiency of Spanish & German